https://great-eastern-sun.com/privacy-policy/

0
Search for:
SHOPMISO MASTER ORGANIC MISOORGANIC BROWN RICE MISOORGANIC CHICKPEA MISOORGANIC COUNTRY BARLEY MISOORGANIC MELLOW WHITE MISOORGANIC SWEET WHITE MISOORGANIC TRADITIONAL RED MISOMISO MASTER MISO TAMARIEMPEROR’S KITCHENGINGER & GARLICLIQUID CONDIMENTSUMEBOSHI CONDIMENTSORGANIC KUZUORGANIC SHIITAKEORGANIC BLACK SESAME SEEDSEMERALD COVE SEA VEGETABLESORGANIC SUSHI NORIORGANIC UNTOASTED NORIPACIFIC ARAMEPACIFIC KOMBUPACIFIC WAKAMEATLANTIC DULSEORGANIC PLANET NOODLESSOBA NOODLESWHOLE WHEAT LOMEINWHOLE WHEAT UDONSUSHI SONIC ASIAN CONDIMENTS100% REAL WASABI POWDER51% REAL WASABI POWDERHAIKU JAPANESE TEASHOJICHA ROASTED GREEN TEAKUKICHA TWIG TEASENCHA GREEN TEASWEET CLOUD BROWN RICE SYRUPPRODUCT INFOORGANIC PLEDGENON-GMO VERIFICATIONKOSHER CERTIFICATIONPRODUCT FLYERSRESEARCHRECIPESHEALTHY RECIPESSUSHI RECIPESMISO RECIPESGES RECIPES by PRODUCTGES RECIPES by COURSEMISO RECIPE COLLECTIONMISO & CHOCOLATERICE SYRUP RECIPESBLOGMEDIAMEDIAPRODUCT FLYERSPRESS RELEASESVIDEOSQ&ACONTACTABOUT USGREAT EASTERN SUN LINKS
PRIVACY POLICYGREAT EASTERN SUN PRIVACY STATEMENT
Who we areGreat Eastern Sun
92 McIntosh Rd
Asheville, NC 28806Phone: 828-665-7790
Email:  customersvc@great-eastern-sun.com
Website: https://great-eastern-sun.comWhat personal data we collect and why we collect itCommentsWhen visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.MediaIf you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.Contact FormsGreat Eastern Sun uses an online Contact Form for the convenience of customers or visitors to contact us with questions, comments… Great Eastern Sun will keep contact form submissions for a certain period for customer service purposes, but you do not use the information submitted through them for marketing purposes of any kind.CookiesIf you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.LEARN MORE ABOUT COOKIES HERE > allaboutcookies.orgEmbedded content from other websitesArticles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.AnalyticsGreat Eastern Sun uses the following services to gather “Analytics” or information to help us to better understand customers and visitors to our website:Google Analytics
InsightsWho we share your data withGreat Eastern Sun shares data with Great Eastern Sun’s marketing and website teams.CUSTOMER DATA:
Authorize.net (secure online payment service) Authorize Privacy Policy
PayPay (secure online payment service) PayPal Privacy PolicyHow long we retain your dataIf you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.How we use your dataRespond to website inquiries
Customer web/online order processing
Provide customer/visitor support and service
Product Giveaways
Monitor site usage and improvementsWhat rights you have over your dataIf you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.Where we send your dataVisitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service. Your contact informationThe following personal information is collected and stored from customer who open a Great Eastern Sun online account:
Great Eastern Sun Customer: name, mailing address, phone number and email email.
Order and payment information.Additional information
How we protect your dataGreat Eastern Sun uses a “managed” hosting service that provides and monitors security of our site and data.What data breach procedures we have in placeGreat Eastern Sun will take immediate action in the case of any data breaches by all the services provided by our hosting service and third party services that we utilize to operate an online market.What third parties we receive data fromGoogle Analytics Privacy PolicyGoogle Analytics Opt-Out Browser Add-On allows website visitors the opt-out of their data used by Google Analytics. Simply click link above and install on your browser. Compatible with Chrome, Internet Exployer 11, Safari, Firefox and Opera.Yoast SEO Premium by Yoast Team / Yoast Privacy Policy
Yoast SEO WooCommerce by Yoast Team / Yoast Privacy Policy MailChimp Email List Service MailChimp Privacy PolicyGreat Eastern Sun Third Party PluginsGoogle Analytics Privacy PolicyMonsterInsights / MonsterInsights Privacy Policy
WooCommerce by Automatic  / WooCommerce Privacy Policy
UPS WooCommerce Shipping by Xadapter / Xadapter Privacy Policy
Yoast SEO Premium by Yoast Team / Yoast Privacy Policy
Yoast SEO WooCommerce by Yoast Team / Yoast Privacy Policy COUPON: $5.00 Off $25 Order when you Sign-Up for our Healthy Table eNewsletterSUBSCRIBE HERE >
